1funny.com 2018-06-28

# Privacy Policy – 1Funny.com

$wpvr_imported array(3) 

'youtube' => array(30) 

'QlJd0sgeoIk' => integer68905

'GrbsHoydkD0' => integer65362

'TddQEzW9MQM' => integer63450

'e-cayNSfZa8' => integer64988

'KwQcrnt2KWw' => integer62067

'0ry8khR922g' => integer51032

'lydVMWcH0lc' => integer51085

'O70Ww9vzjvg' => integer49311

'pmbsVhgJ2FU' => integer49204

'1CjX1r-gh8U' => integer50266

'Q9j0WY91-1o' => integer51184

'e5xSHuO0dJI' => integer62255

'0-O_D-U4YbY' => integer68509

'IaAK0gEoJVk' => integer63721

'Ce-6G-OjKoQ' => integer51009

'hf9tPoF40nQ' => integer64058

'rzkAN3oQjXc' => integer51200

'NOlYdX3-ToE' => integer50995

'qvdFyAI3FEk' => integer50530

'ehAf4-G-840' => integer61422

'kt8AE-mNPUY' => integer61949

'iokOJVtwrck' => integer51935

'LIQD9k2uszo' => integer66517

'5Gww3bczK28' => integer67834

'5IIjFgoRMKU' => integer64387

'FxJD5x_DWaQ' => integer61489

'Uu49lRx1Xf0' => integer61450

'_rB1l2dnVMs' => integer65076

'a8xAkjEqK7k' => integer62360

'Ij89IuE-mjY' => integer63547

'vimeo' => array(0) 

'dailymotion' => array(0) 

wpvr_get_imported_videos() array(3) 

'youtube' => array(30) 

'QlJd0sgeoIk' => integer68905

'GrbsHoydkD0' => integer65362

'TddQEzW9MQM' => integer63450

'e-cayNSfZa8' => integer64988

'KwQcrnt2KWw' => integer62067

'0ry8khR922g' => integer51032

'lydVMWcH0lc' => integer51085

'O70Ww9vzjvg' => integer49311

'pmbsVhgJ2FU' => integer49204

'1CjX1r-gh8U' => integer50266

'Q9j0WY91-1o' => integer51184

'e5xSHuO0dJI' => integer62255

'0-O_D-U4YbY' => integer68509

'IaAK0gEoJVk' => integer63721

'Ce-6G-OjKoQ' => integer51009

'hf9tPoF40nQ' => integer64058

'rzkAN3oQjXc' => integer51200

'NOlYdX3-ToE' => integer50995

'qvdFyAI3FEk' => integer50530

'ehAf4-G-840' => integer61422

'kt8AE-mNPUY' => integer61949

'iokOJVtwrck' => integer51935

'LIQD9k2uszo' => integer66517

'5Gww3bczK28' => integer67834

'5IIjFgoRMKU' => integer64387

'FxJD5x_DWaQ' => integer61489

'Uu49lRx1Xf0' => integer61450

'_rB1l2dnVMs' => integer65076

'a8xAkjEqK7k' => integer62360

'Ij89IuE-mjY' => integer63547

'vimeo' => array(0) 

'dailymotion' => array(0) 

wpvr_is_imported_video(...) boolFALSE

is_singular() boolTRUE

Privacy Policy for 1Funny.com

The privacy of our visitors to 1Funny.com is important to us.

At 1Funny.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit 1Funny.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on 1Funny.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Newsletter / Mailing List  
If you choose to join our newsletter, you will need to enter your email address and an optional name on the newsletter forms on our website. Your email address and name will not be shared with any third party and will strictly be used to send you updates of new content and promotions. Email open and click through data is collected to track the effectiveness of our newsletter. We use GetResponse for hosting our newsletter. [Click here to see their privacy policy](https://www.getresponse.com/legal/privacy.html).

Additional Third Party Plugins and Addons  
This site uses Akismet to reduce spam. [Learn how your comment data is processed](https://automattic.com/privacy-notice/).  
This site uses RhythmOne’s Po.st social sharing plugin. [Click here to see their privacy policy](https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy#).  
This site uses Google Analytics to track visitor data. To see their privacy policy, [click here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).
